[SINGING]
Soft kitty, warm kitty
(Sheldon:)That's for when I'm sick.
Sad is not sick.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know your sad song.
(Sheldon:)I don't have a sad song.
I'm not a child.
(Penny:)Well, you know, I do understand
what you're going through.
Really? Did you have
the Nobel Prize in waitressing...
(Sheldon:)...stolen from you?
(Penny:)Well, no.
But, uh, when I was in high school,
one of my friends heard...
...I was gonna be named
head cheerleader. I was so excited.
(Penny:)My mom even made me
a celebration pie.
(Penny:)Then they named stupid
Valerie Mosbacher head cheerleader.
Big old slutbag.
(Sheldon:)Are you saying
that you think a celebration pie...
(Sheldon:)...is even remotely comparable
to a Nobel Prize?
(Penny:)Well, they're pretty tasty.
(Sheldon:)And on a different
but not unrelated topic...
(Sheldon:)...based on your current efforts
to buoy my spirits...